# Yi Chung Yang

0937-324-826 dumdumgenius@gmail.com Taiwan ,Taichung

### Introduce

Hello, I'm Yi Chung Yang, I come from Taiwan and graduated from Chiao Tung University. I have quick thinking and good knowledge of mathematics and physics, and for most important, I like coding. Although I got my bachelor degree of EE, I chose to start my career as a developer, now I'm a full-stack developer for about two years. I used Java, NodeJS, Ruby to build up back-end, while React.js and Angular.js in front-end. Also I can speak English and some Japanese, I've been looking for a chance to use them to work with people all over the world.

p.s: Must to see my website: <a href="http://www.dumdumgenius.com">http://www.dumdumgenius.com</a>

### Experience

#### TAIPEI, NATURALTEL - 2015 - 2016

Here's my start point as a developer, I used Java to build web application here. Even though I was junior, I took some important missions like mail sender machine and binary files parser, where I used Design Pattern to design and some simple Algorithm.

Followings are the techniques I uses in this Company:

Java, Spring, Hibernate, Tomcat, JavaScript, JQuery, HTML, CSS, Oracle, MySQL, Linux, ShellScript, VXML, SVN

#### **SYNTRONTECH INFORMATION - 2016 - NOW**

In this company, I'm a full-stack engineer. I used JavaScript to build up web application, I took charge with building up a platform, which is used to help customer detect their healthy condition and provide the best health food for them. In this case we used express on back-end and angular.js on front-end, while postgres being our database choice.

Here are the techniques I used:

Angular.js, React.js, Express, Webpack, grunt, gulp, Postgres, git



### Education

Hsinchu, Chiao Tung University – Bachelor, 2009 - 2013

Studied at Electronic Engineering , good at mathematics and I can do quick thinking . I showed great power on coding contest on my department . And that was my first time falling in love with coding.



## **Techniques**

- 1. Nice Language Skill (English, TOEIC: 835), (Japanese, JLPT: N2)
- 2. 2year Experience of Java, JavaScript, also their framework spring and express
- 3. Familiar with front-end framework like Angular, React, and tools like webpack, gulp
- 4. Knowledge about data structure, algorithm
- 5. Server-side rendering, SEO, 3rd-party API
- 6. Postgres database and NoSQL database like Mongo
- 7. Use git, and know the git flow
- 8. Understanding Linux and some usual command

### Reference

Github: <a href="https://github.com/DumDumGeniuss">https://github.com/DumDumGeniuss</a>

Linkedin: https://www.linkedin.com/in/%E4%BA%A6%E4%B8%AD-

%E6%A5%8A-671987b7?trk=hp-identity-name

My Own build Website: <a href="http://www.dumdumgenius.com">http://www.dumdumgenius.com</a>